

Angular Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Angular 4, IONIC Framework, Node. js, GIT, Bootstrap, HTML 5, xml, JavaScript, JSON



Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 0 Month(s) Current Designation: Angular Developer

Current Company: Pricewaterhouse Coopers Private Limited Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Kolkata Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Mumbai, Pune, Bengaluru / Bangalore Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Angular Developer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application

Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Angular 4, IONIC

Framework, GIT, Bootstrap, HTML 5, XML, JavaScript, Angular 8

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Total 3+ years of experience in the field of Web Developing and WebDesigning.

Proficient in finding and resolving malfunctions, using exceptional technical and communication skills.

Ability to express technical concepts clearly to people with no technicalbackground.

Worked on academic project ONLINE MUSICSTORE

An effective communicator with excellent interpersonal, logical thinking & analyticalabilities.

Work Experience

Pricewaterhouse Coopers Private Limited as Angular Developer

May 2020 to Till Date

Working knowledge of front end optimization and performancetechniques.

Makes design recommendations towards the development of new code or reuse of existing code.

Crisp Communication with Clients and work as an interface between team members and Client counterpart.

Developing and Administer the new Angular basedwebsite.

Taking an active role in structuring our single page applications to make them easy to maintain and to ensure they are highly modularized.

Cooperating with the back-end developer in the process of building the RESTFUL API.

PricewaterhouseCoopers Pvt Ltd on behalf of SoftLogique I.T Solutions Pvt. Ltd. as Angular

Developer

Jul 2019 to May 2020

Working knowledge of front end optimization and performancetechniques.

Makes design recommendations towards the development of new code or reuse of existing code.

Crisp Communication with Clients and work as an interface between team members and Client counterpart.

Developing and Administer the new Angular basedwebsite.

Taking an active role in structuring our single page applications to make them easy to maintain and to

ensure they are highly modularized.

Cooperating with the back-end developer in the process of building the RESTFUL API.

Patel Information Technology Services as Web Designer

Jan 2018 to Jun 2019

HTML Coder XML tagging for books and journals Design E-books, Newspapers and Magazines using HTML, XML, CSS, Adobe photoshop Translated necessary requirements into HTMLcode Managed to simultaneously work on multiple projects withoutdeviation Image processing using adobe photoshop

Education

UG: BCA (Computers) from West Bengal University of Technology (WBUT) in 2015

PG: MCA (Computers) from JIS College of Engineering, Kolkata in 2018

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
HTML		2020	1 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
XML		2020	1 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
CSS		2020	1 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
Angular 4+		2020	2 Year(s) 7 Month(s)	
ionic framework	4.0	2019	0 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
Flutter		2020	1 Month(s)	
Node.js		2020	3 Month(s)	
REST API, JQuery		2020		
TypeScript		2020		
JavaScript		2020		
Mongodb		2020		
Git, Bootstrap		2020		

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Proficient			
Bengali	Expert			

Projects

Project Title: ONLINE MUSIC STORE Client: JIS College Of Engineering Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Jul 2018 - Nov 2018

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: ONLINE MUSIC STORE, create using HTML,CSS,AJAX.JSP, where we can buy different type of music.

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time